# **FACHRIZAL KURNIAWAN**

### **FULLSTACK PROGRAMMER**

085244211946 | rizalmc10@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/fachrizal-kurniawan-84255525b/ | https://efkaku.github.io/ .

Yoqyakarta, Indonesia

Bachelor's degree in Information Systems from Amikom University Yogyakarta. Have experience as a system analyst and product owner on mobile and websites when interning in 2022. Apart from that, can use technologies such as CSS, HTML, PHP and basic JavaScript. Currently not working, but taking part in the Full-Stack Web Developer bootcamp program to deepen skills in Web Developer. An individual who is very responsible for the tasks assigned, also committed to providing creative and innovative solutions in web development.

#### Work Experience

PT. BIGIO - Bandung, Indonesia

Aug, 2022 - Des, 2022

System Analyst and Product Owner (Intern)

- · Schedule meetings whenever needed according to Kanban work procedures
- · Carry out analysis and testing on applications that have been developed
- Create specification documents for the application to be worked on
- Perform user analysis for future application improvements
- · make Project Updates every week

## **Project Experiences**

Portofolio - Self Project Jan, 2024 - Apr, 2024

Front End

- Developing some information about myself for someone who needs my strength
- Developed FrontEnd by only using html, css and Js

#### **Education Level**

AMIKOM University - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

2019 - 2023

Bachelor Degree of Information System, 3.86/4.00 (Cumlaude)

- Thesis: Mobile-Based Dzikra Application Development Using Prototype Methods
- Relevant Course Works: Algorithms and data structures, Analysis and design of information system, Advance web programming, E-commerce, Information system concept, Structured programming.

## **Courses, Training and Certifications**

Harisenin.com - Jakarta. Indonesia

Des. 2023 - Mei. 2024

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp, 3.54/4.00

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website for an insurance company, Insurance Technology, within three months
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Native and Node.js
- · Certificate:

### **Skills**

Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, PHP, Codeigniter and Figma

Soft skills: Problem Solving, Public Speaking, Leadership, Time Management, Orientation to Detail, Analytical Thinking and Teamwork

Languages: Indonesian (Native), English (Intermediate)